# EMMANUEL SIMON MMANDA

Address: Sinza C 6, Dar es salaam Twitter: @immaginativetz

Phone: +255 693 123 153 Linkedin https://linkedin.com/in/emma

nuel-mmanda-4a727524b/

Email: luneya17@gmail.com

Website: https://hourlycodes.com

GitHub github.com/EmmanuelMmand

а

#### Education

2013-2017 Uru Seminary O - Level

Pass - Div I

2018-2020 Uru Seminary A- Level

Economics Geography Mathematics - (EGM), Pass Div II

2020 - Now Ardhi BSc.

University Bachelor of Science in Information System Management - Final year

#### Professional Summary

Solution-driven software Developer focused on contributing to a highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions and determining customer satisfaction. Proven experience developing consumer-focused websites using HTML, CSS, Python and JavaScript. Built products for web and mobile users over the years, meeting desired standards for web design, user experience, best practices and speed. Designed and developed web applications and APIs, third-party integrations and databases.

# Experience

2020 - 2021	Ardhi University	Software Development  Participating in University Web Development Team Projects where we developed the Ardhi university Online Voting System
2021 -2022	Ardhi University	Software Development  Participate in University Software project and a Team Lead on project 2 managed to develop an Integrated system for Linking Patients and Herbal medicine providers
2023 -	Ardhi University	Software Development Currently Developing a USSD and SMS integrated System for Village Community Banks (VICOBA) in Tanzania

#### Technical Profile

0	Python , Django , Django
	Rest Framework

 HTML,CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript (React) · GIT, JIRA for Collaboration

- Figma , Adobe XD, Adobe Photoshop
- Third Party Integrations
- · SQL -MySQL , SQLite

· PHP

- Hosting and Deployment -GCP, Vercel, cPanel
- Digital Advertisement -AdSense, Ezoic, AdMob

· CMS - WordPress, SEO

### Languages

SwahiliEnglish

# Hobbies and Interests

Playing Piano and Trumpets

Coding

Self Motivation